<resources>
    <string name="app_name">StudyUp</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">HomeActivity</string>
    <string name="title_home">Study</string>
    <string name="title_words">Profile</string>


    <string name="read1">Three Dog Night</string>
    <string name="read1_content">Three handsome male dogs are walking down the street when they see a beautiful, enticing1, female poodle. The three male dogs fall all over themselves in an effort to be the one to reach her first, but end up arriving in front of her at the same time. The males are speechless before her beauty, slobbering on themselves and hoping for just a glance from her in return.

Aware of her charms and her obvious effect on the three suitors, she decides to be kind and tells them "The first one who can use the words "liver" and "cheese" together in an imaginative, intelligent sentence can go out with me."

The sturdy, muscular black Lab speaks up quickly and says "I love liver and cheese."

"Oh, how childish," said the Poodle. "That shows no imagination or intelligence whatsoever2."

She turned to the tall, shiny Golden Retriever and said, "How well can you do?" "Ummmm…I HATE liver and cheese," blurts3 the Golden Retriever.



"My, my," said the Poodle. "I guess it is hopeless. That is just as dumb as the Lab is sentence."

She then turns to the last of the three dogs and says, "How about you, little guy?"

The last of the three, tiny in stature4 but big in fame and finesse5, is the Taco Bell chihuahua. He gives her a smile, a sly wink6, turns to the Golden Retriever and the Lab and says…</string>

    <string name="read2">Liver and Cheese</string>
    <string name="read2_content">Three handsome male dogs are walking down the street when they see a beautiful, enticing1, female Poodle.

The three male dogs fall all over themselves in an effort to be the one to reach her first, but end up arriving in front of her at the same time.

The males are speechless before her beauty, slobbering on themselves and hoping for just a glance from her in return.

Aware of her charms and her obvious effect on the three suitors, she decides to be kind and tells them, "The first one who can use the words liver and cheese together in an imaginative, intelligent sentence can go out with me."

The sturdy, muscular black Lab speaks up quickly and says, "I love liver and cheese."



"Oh, how childish," said the Poodle. "That shows no imagination or intelligence whatsoever2."

She turns to the tall, shiny Golden Retriever and says "How well can you do?"

"Um. I HATE liver and cheese," blurts3 the Golden Retriever.

"My, my," said the Poodle. "I guess it is hopeless. That is just as dumb as the Lab is sentence."

She then turns to the last of the three dogs and says, "How about you, little guy?"

The last of the three, tiny in stature4 but big in fame and finesse5, is the Taco Bell Chihuahua.

He gives her a smile, a sly wink6, turns to the Golden Retriever and the Lab and says....

Liver alone. Cheese mine.</string>
    <string name="read3">His bride died young</string>
    <string name="read3_content">
        A couple of years ago, his beautiful bride died at an early age,
        but she kept visiting him every night. As the first rays of sunlight shone through the paper screen windows,
        she would leave again. How he wished to be together with her all day long! The young man thought
        long and hard about what he could do to stop her from leaving every morning. At long last, the idea
        came to him of shutting out the sunlight from his room. He at once ordered a tailor to make a large,
        thick curtain that would prevent any sunlight from penetrating1 the window.
        But even so, he failed to keep his bride at home. A strong gust2 of wind blew over a candle
        that was burning near the curtain, igniting3 not only it but also the paper-screen window and,
        finally, everything in the room. There was no time for the husband and his bride to put on their
        clothes; they ran away so fast that no one could catch up with them, and they vanished without a trace.
        As the fire kept burning, the house was consumed by flames and reduced to dust.
        Neither of them were ever seen again.
        Some people said they had gone straight to heaven, while others thought they had gone to hell.
        No one came up with any plausible4 idea, except that everyone was sure both of them turned into
        ghosts and gone far away from the village they used to live. One old man declared it was the bride is
        ghost who asked her husband to go to heaven with her so that they would be able to live a happy life together
        in paradise5 for all eternity6. Another felt it was the husband who was jealous of her happy life and therefore
        lit the fire on purpose. Still another suggested that the bride had a ghost for a boyfriend,
        who was lovesick with missing her every night and found a way to be united with her.
        And there was yet another who thought that, perhaps, the bride was not really happy with her husband
        and lit the fire to kill him.Whatever happened in reality, it is not up to us to prove whose idea
        is right or wrong. Ghosts are the product of human imagination, and no one has ever managed to catch one.</string>
    <string name="read4">The Baby Eagle</string>
    <string name="read4_content">Once upon a time there was a baby eagle living in a nest perched on a cliff overlooking a beautiful valley with waterfalls and streams, trees and lots of little animals, scurrying1 about enjoying their lives.

The baby eagle liked the nest. It was the only world he had ever known. It was warm and comfortable, had a great view, and even better, he had all the food and love and attention that a great mother eagle could provide. Many times each day the mother would swoop2 down from the sky and land in the nest and feed the baby eagle delicious morsels3 of food. She was like a god to him, he had no idea where she came from or how she worked her magic.

The baby eagle was hungry all the time, but the mother eagle would always come just in time with the food and love and attention he craved4. The baby eagle grew strong. His vision grew very sharp. He felt good all the time.



Until one day, the mother stopped coming to the nest.

The baby eagle was hungry. "I am sure to die," said the baby eagle, all the time.

"Very soon, death is coming," he cried, with tears streaming down his face. Over and over. But there was no one there to hear him.

Then one day the mother eagle appeared at the top of the mountain cliff, with a big bowl of delicious food and she looked down at her baby. The baby looked up at the mother and cried "Why did you abandon me? I am going to die any minute. How could you do this to me?"

The mother said, "Here is some very tasty and nourishing food, all you have to do is come get it."

"Come get it!" said the baby, with much anger. "How?"

The mother flew away.

The baby cried and cried and cried.

A few days later, "I am going to end it all," he said. "I give up. It is time for me to die."

He did not know his mother was nearby. She swooped5 down to the nest with his last meal.

"Eat this, it is your last meal," she said.

The baby cried, but he ate and whined6 and whined about what a bad mother she was.

"You are a terrible mother," he said. Then she pushed him out of the nest.

He fell.

Head first.

Picked up speed.

Faster and faster.

He screamed. "I am dying I am dying," he cried. He picked up more speed.

He looked up at his mother. "How could you do this to me?"

He looked down.

The ground rushed closer, faster and faster. He could visualize7 his own death so clearly, coming so soon, and cried and whined and complained. "This is not fair!" he screamed.

Something strange happens.

The air caught behind his arms and they snapped away from his body, with a feeling unlike anything he had ever experienced. He looked down and saw the sky. He was not moving towards the ground anymore, his eyes were pointed8 up at the sun.

"Huh?" he said. "What is going on here!"

"You are flying," his mother said.

"This is fun!" laughed the baby eagle, as he soared and dived and swooped.

"Yes it is!" said the mother.
</string>
    <string name="read5">Annie Chapman is Ghost</string>
    <string name="read5_content">The north side of hanbury street is now covered by the sprawling1 mass of the buildings that were formerly2 the truman brewery3. It was built on the site of number 29 hanbury street, in the back yard of which at around 6am on 8th September 1888, the body of Annie Chapman, jack4 the ripper is second victim was discovered.

At 6am on 8th September 1888 John Davis, an elderly resident of 29 hanbury street came downstairs, walked along the narrow passageway and opened the back door. The sight that he saw shook him to the core. Moments later two workmen walking along hanbury street were suddenly startled when the door of number 29 burst open and a wild eyed old man stumbled into the street. "Men" he cried "come here." Nervously5 they followed him along the passageway and looking into the yard saw the mutilated body of annie chapman.

Her dress had been pulled up around her knees, exposing her striped stockings. A deep cut had slashed6 across her throat; her intestines7 had been tugged8 out and laid across her shoulder. Missing from the body were the uterus and part of the bladder. The contents of her pocket were found lying in a neat pile near to the body. The brass9 rings that she had been wearing at the time of her death had evidently been torn from her fingers and were never discovered. and, just a few feet away from the body, there lay a folded and wet leather apron10.



At 6am on 8th september 1888 john davis, an elderly resident of 29 hanbury street came downstairs, walked along the narrow passageway and opened the back door. The sight that he saw shook him to the core. moments later two workmen walking along hanbury street were suddenly startled when the door of number 29 burst open and a wild eyed old man stumbled into the street. "Men" he cried "come here." Nervously they followed him along the passageway and looking into the yard saw the mutilated body of annie chapman.

Her dress had been pulled up around her knees, exposing her striped stockings. A deep cut had slashed across her throat; her intestines had been tugged out and laid across her shoulder. Missing from the body were the uterus and part of the bladder. The contents of her pocket were found lying in a neat pile near to the body. The brass rings that she had been wearing at the time of her death had evidently been torn from her fingers and were never discovered. And, just a few feet away from the body, there lay a folded and wet leather apron.</string>
    <string name="read6">The goose with the golden eggs</string>
    <string name="read6_content">One morning a countryman went to his goose is nest, and saw a yellow and glittering1 egg there.

He took the egg home. To his delight, he found that it was an egg of pure gold.

Every morning the same thing occurred, and he soon became rich by selling his eggs.

The countryman became more and more greedy. He wanted to get all the gold at once, so he killed the goose, when he looked inside, he found nothing in its body.</string>
    <string name="read7">The old man who did no wrong</string>
    <string name="read7_content">In the countryside, there is a cottage with a thatched roof. There is a shock is nest on the eaves. The wall slopes and there are flowers in the window. They have a pot-bellied stove. In this cottage live an old couple — a peasant and his wife. Even though they are poor, they are not attached to their few possessions. They have a horse.

One day, the old woman says: "Husband, today is the market day. You ride the horse, sell it or exchange it for something else…you will never do anything wrong." The sun is blazing2 hot. There are no clouds in the sky. The road is dusty. What is more, there is no where to shelter. Just then, a man approaches with a cow. The cow is healthy and better than others. "It is sure to make the best milk!" the peasant thinks. "It would be a good buy for me to exchange the cow for the horse…" "Hello, friend." he says. "I think that the hose3 is worth more than the cow, but I do not mind. The cow is more useful to me. Will you trade with me?" "Certainly, I will." The man who is leading the cow says. So they trade. The peasant could have gone home because he had done what he wanted to do. But since he was on his way to the market, he resolves to go and have a look. Therefore, he continues up the road with the cow. In no time, he catches up with a man who is leading a sheep which is nice and fat with good wool. "I want this very much, the peasant thinks in his heart, it can eat the grass beside the ditch. In winter, it can stay with me in the house. Maybe a sheep is better than a cowl. Then the peasant trades the sheep for the cow. After this, he leads the sheep onward4. On the road, he see a man with a big goose under his arm near a fence. " The peasant says: "You have such a big goose! It is feathers are thick and it is fat. If I tie it and put it in the little pond, it is good. My wife can feed it, fruit peels and cabbages. She has often said ‘I want to have a goose. Now she may realize her dream." The man agrees. So they trade. The peasant now owns a goose. He walks into the town. There so many people on the road. The people and the animals are like rabbits in a warren. The peasant comes to a ditch next to the fence of the taxman is potato field. A hen is tied in the field. Seeing this, the peasant thinks: "This hen is the best one which I have seen. It is better than the priest is hen. On my! I want this one. A hen can find grain and fend5 for itself. It will be a good buy if I trade the hen with the goose." "May we trade?" he says. "Trade?" The man says. "Oh, that is not bad." So they trade. The taxman gets the goose and the peasant owns the hen. He has done a lot of business on the way to the market. It is hot and he feels tired. He wants to eat and drink something. He walks toward a tavern6. As he is going in, a seller is coming out. They meet at the gate. "What do you have in the sack?" The peasant asks. "Mashed7 apples" the seller says. "a bag of apples to feed pigs" The peasant say: "There are so many. I wish my wife could see this. Last year, our apple tree just produced three apples. We stored them in the cupboard until it split8 out. It is a fortune. My wife said. Now, she may see quite a fortune. Yes, I wish she could see this." "How much?" the seller asks. "How much? I want trade it with the hen. " So he gets a bag of mashed apples. When he goes into the tavern to the bar, he put the apples near the stove. He does not realize that the fire is burning. There are so many people in the room, including the horseman, the dealer9 and two Englishmen who are very rich. There is a sound: the fire is toasting the apples. "What are those?" Soon they know that the peasant traded the cow with a horse and continued to trade until he got a bag of mashed apples. "Ah, when you go home, I am sure that your wife will hit you", the two Englishmen say, "She will quarrel with you." "She will give me a kiss and she will not hit me." the peasant says, "my wife will say my husband is always correct." They say: "we can bet one hundred and eleven pounds!" The peasant says: "I can juts10 bet a bag of mashed apples. What is more, I may add my wife and myself to the bet. I think that makes it fair." "Good, very good!" they say. So the bet is made. The master drives out his cart. The two Englishmen and the peasant with mashed apples get on it. After a while, they reached the peasants house.

"Good evening, wife!"

"Good evening, husband!"

"I have traded."

"You know what you have done." the old woman says so she hugs him. So they forget all the guests and the apples.

"I traded a cow for the horse."

"Thank goodness, we have milk." the old woman says. "We have milk and cheese. That was a good deal."

"Yes, but I traded a sheep for the cow."

"Ah, that is better!" the old woman says, "That was considerate of you. We have enough grass to raise the sheep. Now I have white cheese and woolen11 socks. Yes, we have woolen night clothes. A cow will not produce so many things. Its hair will fall out. It is considerate of to do that."

"But I traded a goose for it!"

"My dear, we will have goose on St. Martin is festival. You always make me happy. It is a good idea. We may raise the goose which will be fat before the St. Martin is festival. "

"But I traded a hen for it." Her husband says.

"A hen?"

"That was a great deal!" the old woman says. "The hen will lay eggs which will hatch1 into chicks. We just need a brood12 of chicks."

"But I traded a bag of mashed apples for it."

"Now I can not help kissing you." the old woman says, "Thank you, my good husband! Now I will tell you something. As you know, after you left, I planned to cook for you. I remember that pancakes are your favorite food. But I have no caraway seed. So I borrow some from the school teacher. I knew that they had some. But the teacher is wife is so mean. I asked her to lend some to me. Borrow? she says to me. ‘We planted nothing in the vegetable garden besides a mashed apple. We can not lend you because I do not have any apples. Now I can lend her ten mashed apples or a bag of mashed apples. Husband, this is so funny!" She kissed him after saying this.

"This is wonderful!" the two Englishmen say together, "Always he is always meeting misfortune13, he is happy. That is good fortune." Then they pay the peasant 111 pounds because he does not get hit but gets a kiss.
Yes, if an old woman thinks her husband is the cleverest man in the world and says what he does is right, she will gain!
</string>

</resources>
